That's right, guys. You can now automate
your entire portfolio with AI, cryptos
and stocks. And it's finally super easy
to do using Cloud Routines. And I've
been running this with real money. Okay,
but why does it matter and how is it
different from automating with
TradingView? It matters because the AI
can scan the market and find you
opportunities like these and get you in
before the pump happens. It can also
find shorting opportunities, as you can
see here. And that means that this is
useful in market and also in the bear
market. In TradingView, you would have
to pick the coins yourself and then set
up the automation with the trading
alerts. And yes, you can catch these
pumps. But how do you even know that a
coin even matters? Okay, Michael, but
how does it perform? Well, first of all,
it makes money. As you can see here, the
AI opens long and short positions and
manages them fully automatically. And
this is the equity curve of that
strategy. Quite impressive. These are
the KPIs for the Gaussian Channel Trend
Radar that goes long and short. As you
can see here, 7,492%
profit with 35.6%
max drawdown since 2018 1st of January.
Over 2,689
trades, which adds confidence to these
results. As a software engineer and as a
data guy, of course, I care about the
performance and I want to make sure that
it's legit KPIs that I'm looking at and
that's why I ran a massive amount of
simulations before I put my money on the
line and I want to know I'm doing the
right thing. This trading strategy is
described by the trading prompt, which
you can easily copy and use from here.
And the prompt is the trading strategy
now because it contains all of the rules
that the AI has to follow in order to
achieve these KPIs. And it needs the
prompt with the trading rules because it
has to also know which coins to pick and
the position size for each trade. So,
we've leveled up from when to buy and
when to sell to which coin to even trade
and with how much money decided fully
automatically by the AI. There are more
prompts with better KPIs even for stocks
right here which outperforms the S&P 500
in 609 trades also since 2018, but I
will talk more about these prompts later
in the video. Sounds interesting,
Michael, but how hard is this to set up
and can I use it right now? 100%, which
is why I'm making this video. Guys, it's
very easy. We just need to connect
Claude with the Signum MCP. Why Signum?
Because it brings the Trend Radar data
and that's what the AI needs to find the
opportunities in the market. The entire
setup, guys, is very easy and fast, but
I need to explain to you the details so
you know what you're doing, right? So,
first of all, we need to connect the MCP
and then we need to set up the routine
by copy-pasting the prompt from Signum
and picking a schedule so that it runs
once a day fully automatically in the
cloud, okay? So, all of this is very
easy to do. If I do it myself, it takes
60 seconds for the whole thing, but it
will take maybe 10 minutes, maybe 12
minutes to explain it to you. So, get
your coffee, guys, and show some love to
this video. If it blows your mind, click
the like button, subscribe to this
channel for more content like this. This
is not financial advice. Crypto is
risky. You can lose all of your money,
but of course, that's why I'm showing
you AI automation and educate you to do
the right thing. Let's get started.
Okay, guys, let's set this up and as
we're going to connect Claude to Signum
and Signum to HyperLiquid. We are not
going to talk about TradingView because
you already know how to automate
strategies from TradingView and if you
don't know, I will put a video up in the
top right corner. Because anyway, this
is the old way of doing it and using AI
is unlocking all of the benefits I told
you before. So, let's start by creating
a Signum account. For that, simply go to
signum.money and then click on sign up
now. And it's fully free to create the
account. And once you're in Signum,
click on create bot and then click on
futures and then click on hyperliquid.
The reason for futures is because I'm
going to use the prompt that also goes
short and for that I need it to be a
futures account. To create a connection
between Signum and hyperliquid, we have
to go to hyperliquid and create an API
key and that will give us the API wallet
address, the private key and as well
this is the account we're trading with,
the address of that account. And in
order to know how to do all of that, you
have all the explainers right here, how
to create an account on hyperliquid
right here, how to fund the account. You
need to fund it first before you can
actually create an API key, that's how
they do it. And then how to create the
API key, it's all here and we even have
a video specifically about hyperliquid
which I will link in the top right
corner. And if you want to get the 4%
trading fee discount on hyperliquid for
spot and futures, then create your
account using this button. And if you
already have an account, click here on
referrals and then enter Signum. Okay,
now go ahead and create the account,
fund the account and then create the API
key, put the information here, it's all
explained down there like I said. And by
the way, in the creation process of the
bot, you can choose any trading pair you
like, for example ETH USDC because the
AI will change it to what it needs
anyway. And then you have your first
trading bot that is connected to your
account which has funding on it. And in
my case here, I have 100 USDC on it. And
this is the hyperliquid account I have
just connected, here are the 100 USDC
ready to be traded by the AI. And now I
want the AI, specifically Claude, to
have access to these funds and also set
the trading pair it wants to trade
depending on the trading logic and
really manage the entire bot fully
automatically for me. So what we're
doing now is we're connecting Claude to
Signum and telling Claude which of my
bots to use. For that, go back to Signum
and scroll down until you find this box
here, trigger this bot. And how to
trigger this bot, right, is through
TradingView, through your API, but also
through MCP, through the AI itself. And
that's why everything going to need is
going to be here in this MCP tab. So,
click on it to open it up. And then,
let's set up the connection. If you
scroll way down, cuz you need this only
once, right? You will find this URL
here, Claude Connectors. So, click on
this icon to open it up in a new tab.
And here, you set up the connection
between Claude and Signum. So, click
here on plus, click on add custom
connector. You can ignore the advanced
settings. And now, you need to give it a
name, Signum. And the remote MCP server
URL is in Signum. Back in Signum, you
can scroll up a little bit and you will
find it right here. Copy it and paste it
there. Click add. And now, you see that
you need to connect because you also
need to give permissions. So, click
connect. Make sure to be logged into
Signum because this will redirect you
there. And here, you need to keep
everything checked and click allow. And
tada, you have created the connection
successfully and the AI has access to
all of these actions, trend radar data,
and sending trading signals. But even
more than that, you'll be very surprised
what you can do with this, like sending
you an email with all the trades it made
to keep you up-to-date. And also, you
can simply chat with your Signum
account. And you can ask it about the
status of things, how it's doing. And
that's exactly what we're going to do
now because we want to test if this
connection works. And for that, we're
going to go all the way to the left and
click here on new chat. And we're going
to chat with our account. Make sure that
the connector Signum is activated, which
for me it is. And I'm going to choose
Sonnet 4.6. It's totally enough for what
we're doing here. And as well, the
effort level will be medium. There's no
need to spend more tokens. and Sonnet
can even create diagrams in the chat
which the other models cannot for some
reason. So, for me it's the best one for
this use case. So, simply ask it,
"Please summarize my Signum account for
me and show me how my funds are
distributed in a diagram." Let's run
this and see what happens. So, here it
uses the list bots endpoints so that it
can fetch all my bots, right? So, what
it's doing right now is scanning through
all of my bots and fetching the assets
and then hopefully summarizing them
nicely. Now it has all the data, it
wants to approximate the US dollar value
of all of those assets that I hold in
there. Then that's very helpful because
later on it can do a pie chart and show
me how my money is distributed. And as
you can see here, it creates these nice
boxes and I think here we might get a
diagram. Yeah, there you go. So, this is
just from asking it one simple question
to summarize my Signum account and this
is not even trading yet, but it's
already very useful to know how your
trading bots are performing, what
they're doing, and simply asking it even
from the mobile app what is going on in
your trading account and that's possible
because you have connected Claude with
Signum and Claude has full access to
everything you would have access to as
well. Just that it's fully automatic and
it can do it for you. So far so good,
everything works, but now what we want
to do is we want Claude to trigger
itself periodically with the trading
prompt and then get access to the bot,
understand which assets are there, and
make the necessary trades based on the
trend radar, right? So, the difference
here is that instead of us triggering
it, okay, by going to the chat, we going
to use the routines and the routines,
they can run in a schedule and that's
why they can run when we are doing other
things. It's fully automatic, right?
Let's set up the routine. This is the
trade automation now with the prompt.
For that, we go back to Signum and we
open up the bot we want to use for this
automation. We scroll down and we click
on the MCP tab because again, everything
you need for the MCP is in that tab. And
now, we're going to use the routines URL
here. We're going to open it up, so
click on this button to open it up in a
new tab. And this is how it looks for
me, but you might have to go through a
wizard before you can use this. We need
to do some setup before the setup. So,
let's click on continue on web. Click on
get started. Click on connect different
way. Click on skip this step and click
on create and finish. We just want to
get through the setup process so we can
finally access the routines. The
routines are part of Claude code and
that means you need the pro plan or
above. Okay, now the fun starts because
finally we can automate with AI. So,
here click on the button on the top
right saying new routine. And you need a
name. Go back to the Signum bot and you
can copy the name from here. Paste it
into the Claude routine. And now, you
need to give it the instructions which
is the trading prompt which is the
trading strategy. So, go back to Signum,
scroll up and copy this prompt right
here. It's the Trend Radar Gaussian
Channel Crypto Long and Short Version 2.
If the version updates, then you will
see when it was updated and as well it
will have a higher version number. It
would have three, for example. So, I
recommend you check this out once in a
while so you always use the last
version. So now, click on copy AI prompt
and paste it here into the Claude
routine. Notice when you scroll up that
your bot ID is already in the prompt, so
make sure you're using the right bot for
this. Meaning, the one that you want to
use for this crypto automation. And now,
make sure to choose Sonnet 4.6. It's the
model we had the best experiences with.
And then, choose a schedule. And I want
you to make sure this is running at half
past midnight UTC time. And that depends
on your time zone. So, I'm in Dubai
right now, so 4:00 a.m. in the morning
is 00 UTC. And I will run this half an
hour after that. And the reason for that
is that the prompt relies on the trend
radar data, which gets updated on a
daily basis and it takes about 15 to 20
minutes to update it. And I want to make
sure that my trading automation, the
prompt, runs after the latest data is
available. And then simply make sure
that the Signum connector is there and
remove all the other connectors to save
on tokens. And the only thing left to do
is to click create and that makes it
fully automatic. Now, the AI will
execute this trading prompt with all the
rules that it has inside, as you can see
here, when to exit longs, when to exit
shorts, when to go long, when to go
short. All the stuff is written there in
plain English. You can read it yourself
to understand what it's doing. And it
will execute itself every day at this
hour and it will even send you a summary
email once it's done because that's what
it says in the prompt. This is how the
email looks like and is super helpful in
the morning when I wake up to see what
my AI automations did. It tells me the
value of my portfolio in dollars, net
asset value. It tells me which trades it
made, closing trades, opening trades. As
you can see, it entered quite a lot of
short positions because we're in a bear
market right now. So, this email is very
helpful. And this is how it looks for
me. As you can see here, it's scheduled
and it runs every day executing this
prompt to scan the market and trade this
portfolio for me. Of course, I have
multiple of those set up, but let's
click on one of these executions and see
how they look like. And this is how it
looks like when the AI is executing that
prompt. You're not going to see it until
you click on it because the AI is really
talking to itself, but later on you can
come here and you can check what it was
doing. It wants to trade Atom, right?
So, first of all, it has to set the
trading pair for Atom and then send the
trading signal and it does that for all
of the assets it wants to trade. And
then this is a summary and then I get
the email and the whole thing starts all
over again tomorrow. But now, let's go
back to our routine and run this prompt
now and remember we have a bot connected
which has 100 USDC. Let's see how it
will be trading this and while it is
processing, let me show you something
cool. These are one of the first
reactions from people using the AI
automation. As you can see here,
mind-blowing. This user here says, "Wow,
wow, wow." It converted USDC to USDT
because it needed it to trade a coin. It
did that fully automatically. And this
user here saying that the AI stuff is
amazing that well, I'm on fire and that
this group just went on another level.
And of course, I'm happy to hear that,
but now let's see what the AI did here
with our trading prompt execution. As
you can see here, there is nothing to go
long on which makes sense. The market is
pretty bearish, but there is something
to go short on, but it could not do that
because I have not enough money on my
account. Because remember, I have 100
USDC here, which you can also see in the
connected Signum bot. And it wanted to
go short on Uniswap with 5% of net asset
value. That would be worth $5, but we
have a limit to the downside. We have to
trade with more than $10. It's part of
the prompt. You can change if you want,
but basically that is dust and that's
why it skipped that order. It also
wanted to go short on meme core, but
there is no tradeable pair on this
exchange to trade that coin, so it
skipped that, which is perfect. So you
see, I made a mistake. I should have put
200 USDC in there because then this
order would go through. So the minimum
that you need to trade this prompt is
200 USDC. So I went back to HyperLiquid
and now I have 200 USDC on it, which I
can also see in Signum when I reload the
bot page. And when I run this routine
again, then you can see the AI opened a
short position and well, it's already in
profit, but that's just coincidence.
Congratulations, you have just automated
your entire crypto portfolio with AI,
which I think it's going to be a
game-changer for you. And if you want to
upgrade your trading game and you want
more than these two prompts, then
consider joining the auto trading master
class because then you get access to all
of these prompts, especially this one
which is at 12,226%
net profit. And as well, for people with
higher portfolios, we have this prompt
here which has a very low drawdown when
you think about that this prompt is
trading the riskiest part of crypto,
also making 8,417%
since 2018. And people who want to beat
the S&P 500 also get the stocks prompt,
which is at 506% P&L with a very low
drawdown over the time frame because
this is buy and hold on S&P 500 and it
made only 178% profit with 18.82% max
drawdown, which is worse on every metric
compared to our prompt. In the auto
trading master class, you learn way more
than just these prompts. Of course, this
is my entire system on how to automate
your portfolio and how to do risk
management. So, if you care about that,
then go to auto trading VIP and check
out what I say in this video, read the
reviews, do your research. This is not
for everyone. You need it when you need
it, not before. And once you have access
to it, it's of course a total
game-changer, which you can see in the
reviews. So, if you like what you're
hearing on this website when you watch
the video, then make sure to click on
apply for access and if there is a
match, you can join. Holy moly, guys.
Congratulations. You just learned how to
automate your entire portfolio with AI.
And this is just the beginning. And
yeah, it's mind-blowing. I'm automating
my portfolio like this, but not just
like this because for the big coins,
okay, the ones that I think can be
automated with my personal trading
strategy, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Solana, and
some others, I don't use AI for that.
And if you want to know why, then ask me
down below and as well, come to the
Telegram group. We can talk about all of
this over there, especially if you have
further questions, if you need a help,
the link will be down below. And if you
want to know why buy and hold is the
worst possible strategy for risk assets,
then this is the next video you must
watch.
>> It's trading view.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
>> [music]
>> Oh, yeah.
Strategies, we know what to do.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> [music]
>> Stop loss set, watch the price rise and
fall.